The Witness is a documentary film directed by James Solomon.
A brother's journey to unravel the truth about the mythic death and little known life of Kitty Genovese, who
was reportedly murdered in front of 38 witnesses and has become the face of urban apathy.
Himself, played by William Genovese.
Herself, played by Shannon Beeby.
Herself (archive footage), played by Kitty Genovese.
Herself, played by Catherine Pelonero.
The Witness (Chinese: 我是证人) is a 2015 crime thriller film
directed by Ahn Sang-hoon, starring Yang Mi and Lu Han.
The film is a remake of the 2011 South Korean film
Blind, also by the same director.
It was released in China on October 30, 2015.
The film explores themes of witness, interview,
biography, based on true story, murder.